ICICI Lombard's Q3 results are coming out on the 17th, so let's talk about
how the Q3 results will be. So
let's start the video.
[Music]
So if we look at its quarter-by-quarter
performance, you will see that sales are increasing
every quarter,
which is a very
good thing. At the same time, if you
look at expenses, they are increasing significantly here.
Expenses are also increasing significantly,
competing with sales,
due to which we will see its operating profit decreasing
significantly here. The
company had made a loss, but now it is
gradually making a profit again and
its profit also seems to be increasing.
Talking about the same from the last quarter, if we
talk about its quarterly
profit and loss account, if we
look at its overall performance, then we see that its sales are
increasing significantly here.
If we talk about expenses, the
same thing happens that expenses are
increasing significantly.  If the company is
doing good sales, then the expenses in the company are also increasing a lot, due to which the
operating profit here is
not as good
as we could have seen because the
sales are getting quite good, like you
will see that in the last 20-21, when you see
that we got sales of 12000 here,
but the expenses were 10000, due to which
its operating
profit was seen to be around 1500,
but if you look at the profit and loss of this company, then
you will see that
yearly the sales of the company are
increasing very well, but
along with that, the expenses of the company are also increasing a
lot, the effect of which we are
seeing in the operating profit, well the
company is making profit, but its
performance is not that good here, so if
you look at it from a key point of view, then if the
company
is performing well, its
operating profit also increases.  If
we are seeing it then we can say
that there are 50-50% chances that the
result we will get can be positive as well as negative
or even average, the way
we are getting to see the performance in it, we can get to see
similar numbers,
what happens tomorrow and what kind of
result we will get to see, so that's all for
today's video,
like the video, share it, subscribe to the channel,
thank you so much for watching
this video.